<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>profile on Muhammad Daffa</title>
    <link>https://daffa.info/tags/profile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in profile on Muhammad Daffa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://daffa.info/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://daffa.info/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daffa.info/tags/profile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://daffa.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daffa.info/about/</guid>
      <description>Muhammad Daffa Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Muhammad Daffa, but you can call me Daffa. I began delving into cybersecurity around 2019 to 2020. My interest sparked when some of my Facebook friends posted about making money through an activity known as &amp;lsquo;bug bounty.&amp;rsquo; Intrigued by their posts, I embarked on a journey to learn more about cybersecurity, with a specific focus on website penetration testing.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t mistake me for a professional penetration tester just yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVEs</title>
      <link>https://daffa.info/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daffa.info/cve/</guid>
      <description>These are some of the CVEs I obtained from conducting penetration testing.
CVEs CVE-2023-25989 CVE-2022-47172 CVE-2022-47169 CVE-2023-23823 CVE-2022-45372 CVE-2022-33974 CVE-2022-47174 CVE-2022-47136 CVE-2022-47178 CVE-2022-47137 CVE-2022-45371 CVE-2022-33961 CVE-2022-32970 CVE-2022-45367 CVE-2022-47149 CVE-2022-47161 CVE-2023-28989 CVE-2022-46793 CVE-2022-46795 CVE-2022-46794 CVE-2023-27461 CVE-2023-26543 CVE-2022-46851 CVE-2022-46853 CVE-2022-46852 CVE-2022-40198 CVE-2022-47166 CVE-2022-46855 CVE-2022-46797 CVE-2022-46796 CVE-2022-46798 CVE-2022-46848 CVE-2022-45068 CVE-2023-23711 CVE-2022-45376 CVE-2022-45076 CVE-2022-47148 CVE-2022-47170 CVE-2023-22700 CVE-2022-45067 CVE-2022-26366 CVE-2022-25952 CVE-2022-43481 CVE-2022-43463 CVE-2022-36401 CVE-2022-43488 CVE-2022-40686 CVE-2022-40687 CVE-2022-41805 CVE-2022-34148 CVE-2022-43491 CVE-2022-38137 CVE-2022-32776 CVE-2022-34654 CVE-2022-32587 CVE-2022-36340 CVE-2022-40132 CVE-2022-38134 CVE-2022-40194 CVE-2022-38470 CVE-2022-38095 CVE-2022-33177 CVE-2022-38058 CVE-2022-36282 CVE-2022-35726 CVE-2022-38703 CVE-2022-34347 CVE-2022-36346 CVE-2022-38704 CVE-2022-33201 CVE-2022-27848 CVE-2022-27844 CVE-2022-25618 CVE-2022-23983 CVE-2022-23984 CVE-2021-24561 CVE-2021-24531 CVE-2021-24519 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://daffa.info/bug-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daffa.info/bug-hunting/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my achievements when doing bug hunting
Bug Bounties and Hall of Fame Sekolah Siber Wageningen University &amp;amp; Research PostNL Holding B.V Inflectra Legally Breaking (Website Inactive) DIB-VDP Pilot (Program Closed) PlanetArt Automattic Valve Yelp 2 Private Program at Hackerone Certificate Appreciation Axioo Class Program GeeksforGeeks Cambridge University Windesheim University Finansialku PixelNinja ID Bitrexgo (Website Inactive) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://daffa.info/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daffa.info/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my portfolios on cybersecurity
Bug Bounties The list below are some of the companies that recognize me as a bug hunter. Here are 5 achievements that I just got
Hall of Fame at Sekolah Siber Hall of Fame at wur.nl Thanks list at HackerOne PlanetArt Thanks list at HackerOne Valve Certificate Appreciation from GeeksforGeeks Click here to see the full list
CVEs Here is a list of CVEs that I got, most of them came from vulnerabilities in wordpress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
